innovastudio.com 2018-06-02

# InnovaStudio Content Builder (ContentBuilder.js) - Privacy

Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. At InnovaStudio.com, we want to make your experience online satisfying and safe. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting InnovaStudio.com, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy notice.

We receive, collect and store any information you enter on our website or provide us in any other way. 

We may use software tools to measure and collect session information, including Internet protocol (IP) address, page response times, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information, and methods used to browse away from the page. 

When you conduct a transaction on our website, as part of the process, we collect personal information you give us such as your name, address and email address. 

We collect such non-personal and personal Information for the following purposes: 

  * To provide and operate the services;
  * To provide our users with ongoing customer assistance and technical support;
  * To be able to contact our visitors and users with general or personalized service-related notices and promotional messages;
  * To create aggregated statistical data and other aggregated and/or inferred non-personal Information, which we or our business partners may use to provide and improve our respective services;
  * To comply with any applicable laws and regulations.

We may contact you to notify you regarding your account, to troubleshoot problems with your account, to resolve a dispute, to collect fees or monies owed, to poll your opinions through surveys or questionnaires, to send updates about our company, or as otherwise necessary to contact you to enforce our User Agreement, applicable national laws, and any agreement we may have with you. 

If you would like to: access, correct, amend, delete any personal information we have about you or if you don’t want us to process your data anymore, please contact us at support@innovastudio.com. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website.
